[
  {
    "question": "All unit tests are executed daily and ideally should be automated.",
    "choices": [
      "No answer text provided.",
      "XP Design",
      "XP Coding",
      "XP Testing"
    ],
    "answer": "XP Testing"
  },
  {
    "question": "This is different customers' needs need to be assimilated. Different vision or beyond their authority.",
    "choices": [
      "Lack of formal design",
      "Lack of program design",
      "Conflicting customer needs",
      "Requirements volatility"
    ],
    "answer": "Conflicting customer needs"
  },
  {
    "question": "“demos” are not delivered to the customer with the time-box allocated. May not contain all functionalities.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The development guidelines stress delivery over analysis and design although these activates are not discouraged, and active and continuous communication between developers and customers.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Delivers multiple ‘software increments’, deliver an operational prototype or portion of an OS to collect customer feedback for adaption.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Delivers multiple ‘software decrements’, deliver an operational prototype or portion of an OS to collect customer feedback for adaption.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Agile processes harness change for the customer's competitive advantage.",
    "choices": [
      "Welcome changing",
      "eliver working software frequently",
      "satisfies the customer",
      "satisfies the employer"
    ],
    "answer": "Welcome changing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The most efficient and ineffective method of conveying information too and within a development team is face–to–ear conversation.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Collaboration and consensus occur when the collective knowledge of members of the team is combined.",
    "choices": [
      "Take notes and document decisionsTake notes and document decisions",
      "Stay focused, modularize your discussion",
      "Strive for collaboration",
      "Stay focus on the customer needs"
    ],
    "answer": "Strive for collaboration"
  },
  {
    "question": "The information domain of a problem must be represented and understood.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Component-level design should be functionally independent.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The design should be developed iteratively. With each iteration, the designer should strive for greater simplicity.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The construction activity encompasses a set of coding and testing tasks that lead to operational software that is ready for delivery to the customer or end-user.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lots of things can go wrong as software is being developed.",
    "choices": [
      "Assess Risk",
      "Build an effective team",
      "Manage Change",
      "No answer text provided."
    ],
    "answer": "Assess Risk"
  },
  {
    "question": "The approach may be either formal or informal, but mechanisms must be established to manage the way changes are requested, assessed, approved and implemented.",
    "choices": [
      "No answer text provided.",
      "Manage Change",
      "Assess Risk",
      "Build an effective team"
    ],
    "answer": "Manage Change"
  },
  {
    "question": "The process molds to the _______ and team, not the other way around.",
    "choices": [
      "working software",
      "needs of people",
      "self–organizing"
    ],
    "answer": "needs of people"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ XP deemphasizes the need for architectural design.",
    "choices": [
      "Requirements volatility",
      "Conflicting customer needs",
      "Lack of formal design",
      "No answer text provided."
    ],
    "answer": "Lack of formal design"
  },
  {
    "question": "Testing and documentation are on-going as the product is constructed.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is our highest priority through early and continuous delivery of valuable software.",
    "choices": [
      "Welcome changing",
      "satisfies the customer",
      "deliver working software frequently",
      "No answer text provided."
    ],
    "answer": "satisfies the customer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leading a team so that it is in control of the work performed.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The only really important work product is an operational “software increment” that is delivered.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Someone participating in the communication should serve as a “recorder” and write down all important points and decisions.",
    "choices": [
      "Strive for collaboration",
      "Take notes and document decisions",
      "Stay focused on the customer needs",
      "Stay focused, modularize your discussion"
    ],
    "answer": "Take notes and document decisions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Design models represent characteristics of the software that help practitioners to construct it effectively.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The analysis task should move from essential information toward implementation detail.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Components should be loosely coupled to one another and to the external environment.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Design representations (models) should be easily understandable.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The construction activity encompasses a set of coding and testing tasks that lead to operational software that is ready for delivery to the customer or end-user.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "A software development method Originally proposed by Schwaber and Beedle (an activity occurs during a rugby match) in early 1990.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "“demos” are delivered to the customer with the time-box allocated. May not contain all functionalities.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Our highest priority is to satisfy the customer through early and continuous delivery of valuable software.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Deliver working software frequently, from a couple of weeks to a couple of months, with a preference to the shorter timescale.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Separation of concerns (Principle #1) establishes a philosophy for software.",
    "choices": [
      "Build software that exhibits effective modularity",
      "Focus on the transfer of information",
      "Look for patterns.",
      "Take notes and report"
    ],
    "answer": "Build software that exhibits effective modularity"
  },
  {
    "question": "Try to focus on the speaker’s words, rather than formulating your response to those words.",
    "choices": [
      "Prepare for customer needs",
      "Someone should facilitate the activity",
      "Prepare you communicate",
      "Listen"
    ],
    "answer": "Listen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Design of data is as important as design of processing functions.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "User interface design should be tuned to the needs of the end-user. However, in every case, it should stress ease of use.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The modern business environment is fast-paced and ever-changing.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The most efficient and effective method of conveying information to and within a development team is face–to–face conversation",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the primary measure of progress.",
    "choices": [
      "working software",
      "Efficiency and Effectiveness",
      "Self–organizing",
      "Simplicity"
    ],
    "answer": "working software"
  },
  {
    "question": "Every communication meeting should have a leader (a facilitator) to keep the conversation moving in a productive direction.",
    "choices": [
      "Prepare for customer needs",
      "Someone should facilitate the activity",
      "Listen",
      "Prepare you communicate"
    ],
    "answer": "Someone should facilitate the activity"
  },
  {
    "question": "User interface design should be not tuned to the needs of the end-user. However, in every case, it should distress ease of use.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Testing principles and concepts lead to the design of tests that systematically uncover different classes of errors and to do so with a minimum amount of time and effort.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stated in a more technical manner, analysis and design should always emphasize separation of concerns (SoC).",
    "choices": [
      "Understand the use of abstraction",
      "No answer text provided.",
      "Strive for consistency",
      "Divide and conquer"
    ],
    "answer": "Divide and conquer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Speculation project is initiated and adaptive cycle planning is conducted.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Emphasize an incremental delivery strategy as opposed to intermediate products that gets working software to the customer as rapidly as feasible.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is from a couple of weeks to a couple of months, with a preference to the shorter timescale.",
    "choices": [
      "deliver working software frequently",
      "satisfies the employer",
      "Welcome changing",
      "satisfies the customer"
    ],
    "answer": "deliver working software frequently"
  },
  {
    "question": "______ is a broad array of principles, concepts, methods and tools that you must consider as software is planned and developed.",
    "choices": [
      "Software Process",
      "Software Application",
      "Software Engineer",
      "Software Practice"
    ],
    "answer": "Software Practice"
  },
  {
    "question": "Design of data is as important as design of processing non-functions.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Component-level design should be non- functionally independent.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The construction activity encompasses a set of coding and testing tasks that is not lead to operational software that is not readyfor delivery to the customer or end-user.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The development guidelines stress delivery over analysis and design although these activates are discouraged, and active and has no continuous communication between developers and customers",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ customer is an active member of XP team, changes to requirements are requested informally and frequently.",
    "choices": [
      "Conflicting customer needs",
      "Lack of program design",
      "Lack of formal design",
      "Requirements volatility"
    ],
    "answer": "Requirements volatility"
  },
  {
    "question": "Brad Appleton [App00] suggests that: “The goal of patterns within the software community is to create a body of literature to help software developers resolve recurring problems encountered throughout all of software development.",
    "choices": [
      "Focus on the customer",
      "Look for patterns.",
      "Focus on the transfer of information",
      "Build software that exhibits effective modularity"
    ],
    "answer": "Look for patterns."
  },
  {
    "question": "Design models represent characteristics of the software that will not help practitioners to construct it effectively.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Encourages _______ an iterative refinement of the internal program design.",
    "choices": [
      "spike solution",
      "refactoring",
      "No answer text provided.",
      "self–organizing"
    ],
    "answer": "refactoring"
  },
  {
    "question": "Organizing a team so that it is in control of the work performed.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Testing principles and concepts lead to the design of tests that systematically cover different classes of not free for errors and to do so with a minimum amount of time and effort.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The functions that the software performs must be defined.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The analysis task should not move from essential information toward implementation detail",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Components should be loosely coupled to other components and to the internal environment.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The more people involved in any communication, the more likely that discussion will bounce from one topic to the next.",
    "choices": [
      "Take notes and document decisions",
      "Take notes and report",
      "Stay focused, modularize your discussion",
      "Strive for collaboration"
    ],
    "answer": "Stay focused, modularize your discussion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Conventional wisdom is that the cost of change decrease linear as a project progresses.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Deliver working software frequently, from a couple of days to a couple of months, with no preference to the shorter timescale.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Give them the environment and support they need, and trust them to get the job done.",
    "choices": [
      "Satisfy customer",
      "Satisfy employer",
      "Face-to-face",
      "Motivated Individual"
    ],
    "answer": "Motivated Individual"
  },
  {
    "question": "A software development method Originally proposed by Schwaber and Beedle (an activity occurs during a rugby match) in early 1992.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The models that depict information, function, and behavior must be partitioned in a manner that uncovers detail in a layered (or hierarchical) fashion.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The only really important work product is an operational “software decrement” that is not delivered.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pay special attention to the analysis, design, construction, and testing of interfaces.",
    "choices": [
      "Look for patterns.",
      "Build software that exhibits effective modularity",
      "Focus on the customer",
      "Focus on the transfer of information"
    ],
    "answer": "Focus on the transfer of information"
  },
  {
    "question": "Software engineering process and practice are important, but the bottom line is people.",
    "choices": [
      "No answer text provided.",
      "Manage Change",
      "Assess Risk",
      "Build an effective team"
    ],
    "answer": "Build an effective team"
  },
  {
    "question": "Define Conventional wisdom.",
    "choices": [
      "No answer text provided.",
      "the cost of change increases nonlinearly as a project progresses.",
      "The development guidelines stress delivery over analysis and design although these activates are not discouraged, and active and continuous communication between developers and customers.",
      "the art of maximizing the amount of work not done – is essential."
    ],
    "answer": "the cost of change increases nonlinearly as a project progresses."
  },
  {
    "question": "Our highest priority is to satisfy the customer through early and continuous delivery of non-valuable software.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  }
]